The changing room is
way too far from the venue...
Maybe it's careless to attend a cosplay
event in the same town where I work.
Well, considering all the foot traffic,
and that it's in the opposite direction from
the office, and it's a day off...
Cosplay Event Reception
On the Left
I doubt I'll run into anyone.
Huh? Hayakawa-san?
What a coincidence,
running into you on a day off.
What's up?
My name is Hayakawa Chinatsu, 22 years old...
I'm an office worker in my
first year of employment.
And my boss just found out
about me being an otaku.
Oh, I love you so much, I just have to laugh
My Tiny Senpai
We've got an emergency here
Are you paying attention, me?
There's someone other than me
dancing around inside of my heart
I want to talk to her
I want to touch her
Look, I get it, but for now try to pipe down
What in the world am I doing?
You're right next to me
And this is the perfect chance...
HONEY
I'm trapped by that sweet rich taste
And I don't think I can ever escape
I may as well just sink into it
HONEY
It's another day in your dazzling presence
We may never be
on the same page with this love but
Oh, I love you so much, I just have to laugh
#04 When It Comes to Him, I'm Not Sure Yet...
What are you up to, Hayakawa-san?
Y-You've got the wrong person!
I-I'm not Hayakawa, Manager!
You just called me your manager.
Cosplay Event Reception
On the Left
Of all the people...
The manager is like the textbook
definition of a normie, too!
Huh. A cosplay event? I see.
Hayakawa-san.
Y-Yes?
Where do you buy an outfit like that?
W-Well, I-I actually made it myself.
I'm done.
It's all over for me...
He's probably wondering
why a grown woman is doing
something like this and thinks it's creepy.
I have to say, Hayakawa-san...
Here it comes! The words every otaku dreads!
I don't wanna hear it! I don't wanna
hear my manager call me creepy!
That's pretty cool, Hayakawa-san.
It is?
Yeah. I think it's really cool.
Wait, how?! What about this is cool?
Your approach to life, maybe?
A-All that?!
I don't have any hobbies,
so I respect people who do,
like you. I think it's pretty cool.
Then again, that outfit
is more cute than cool.
How can he just up and say
something like that?!
What's wrong?
N-Nothing, th-thank you.
Manager! Please don't tell anyone about this.
Is it supposed to be a secret?
Please!
But it's really impressive.
That's a matter of opinion.
A-Anyway...
Let's keep this a secret,
just between us. Please.
Cute!
Why would you say it again?!
Well...
The first one was more about
your costume and how you look,
and the second one was more about
you personally, Hayakawa-san.
I didn't want an actual explanation!
I didn't hear anything
you just said! Not a thing!
But it's true that you're—
Like! I! Said!
I heard nothing!
I love you.
The deadline for Comiket
submissions is coming up...
But I can't focus.
I can't believe my boss
found out that I'm a cosplayer.
I asked him to keep quiet,
and I doubt he'd blab, but...
I wonder if there's a pressure point
to erase someone's memory...
Where am I? What are you?
How did this even happen?
Work is going to be a nightmare tomorrow.
Senpai!
I'd like you to review the materials I put
together for the upcoming project submission.
Sure! I'll take a look.
Let's see here...
Yep, you covered
your bases nicely! Well done.
Th-Thank you.
Didn't get anywhere with my manuscript...
Didn't sleep much...
This really sucks...
Hayakawa. Hey, Hayakawa?
You okay? You look worn out.
Oh, er, I-I'm totally fine!
It's just, a bunch of stuff happened
yesterday... and I didn't get much sleep.
A lack of sleep can contribute
to all kinds of health problems.
Be careful, okay?
When you can't sleep, try counting cats!
One kitty,
two kitties,
three kitties,
I think most people use sheep...
four kitties—
No! Cats are fine, too.
Thanks for the concern, Katase-san.
Hayakawa-san...
Are you not feeling well? Everything okay?
M-Manager?!
Uh, well... er... yes, I-I'm okay.
Okay. In that case, would you like to
join me for dinner tonight?
I was hoping we could talk.
In a nice, quiet restaurant.
Just the two of us,
if that's all right.
Dinner for j-just the two of us?!
You mean like...
Cute... Cute... Cute...
W-Well...
a-as long as we're done before the last train.
Sounds great.
Let me know when
you're done work.
Okay.
Is this a date?
I-It isn't!
Sounds suspicious!
Well, it's not!
Right.
This isn't a date or anything like that.
My boss just... asked me out...
for a bit of dinner.
It's nothing.
It's not a big deal!
Sorry about the wait.
You okay?
W-Well... er...
Thanks for the save.
Don't mention it. Watch your step, now.
Okay.
Speaking of... when you came for your
employment test, didn't you break a heel?
You remember that?
Of course I do.
That must've been rough.
But I'm glad you passed,
and now we get to work together.
He remembered...
Now, let's get a move on, Hayakawa-san.
O-Okay.
I'd think you're used to the office by now,
but do you have any issues
or things you're worried about?
No. Everyone is really nice,
so nothing comes to mind.
Well, that's good to hear.
The section chief mentioned
how impressed he was
with how much faster you've gotten.
Come on, it's nothing that impressive.
All he's brought up
during dinner is work stuff,
so I guess this is more like
a dinner meeting than anything.
Manager, didn't you mention
something you wanted to discuss?
Right.
Hayakawa-san...
I know this might surprise you
coming out of the blue, but...
Hayakawa-san...
when I look at you, I got really excited.
I've never felt this way before,
and I'm not sure if it's fair
to spring this on you...
Hang on... is this... is he...?!
Hayakawa-san!
Y-Yes?!
I'd like to attend a cosplay event with you!
I mean, when I think about
how you made that costume,
I get excited thinking about
how much fun it must be!
That's what you meant?!
Well... are you saying you
want to cosplay, too, Manager?
Nope. When I went home
and started looking into it,
I found out about photo sessions
they have for cosplay, and well...
I'd love to capture your exploits with this!
What a scary combo of initiative
and purchasing power!
I-I mean, you could just take pictures
of whatever cosplay you want.
You don't need me for that...
But you were the one who made me
realize it'd be fun, Hayakawa-san.
I want it to be you.
It's not fair how he can just say stuff
like that with a straight face...
The month after next,
there's going to be an event
at the same location, so if you want...
Oh, but in exchange, you need the check out
the things my costumes are from!
Real otaku always proselytize
Otherwise you can't take pictures!
Cute.
How?!
None of that was cute at all!
Yes, it was. The way you're so earnest
about talking about the things you like.
It was very c—
No more explanations!
But you're the one who was—
I do not want to hear it at all!
Not another word!
Shinozaki, you wanna grab lunch?
Sure. Let me just finish this up.
Got it.
You need to talk?
Well... yeah.
Okay, one sec. I'll be right there.
I'll wait in the lobby.
Y'know, Hayakawa-san and Shinozaki-kun
seem closer than regular coworkers.
Apparently, they're childhood friends
who grew up as neighbors.
Oh, right. I remember
hearing about that, now.
Are you interested in what's going on?
Katase-san, there's no need to get giddy.
Since you always pick on me,
I'm just glad for a chance at payback!
Hayakawa-san might've denied it before,
but maybe there is actually a chance...
Or the
reunited
childhood
friends/
classmates
romance.
A reunited childhood
friends/classmates romance.
The age-gap
romance
between
a senpai
and kohai
at work.
An age-gap romance
between a senpai and kohai at work.
Which one am I supposed to root for?!
Sh-Sh-Shinozaki-san and I aren't like that...
More importantly, Manager!
Aren't you forgetting an option?
Another option...?
There's nothing like another girl.
H-Hayakawa-san...
Of course.
Why would you take it that way?!
You brought it up, Katase-san,
but aren't you curious about what's going on
with Shinozaki-kun and Hayakawa-san?
N-Not really. The two of them
can be as friendly as they want...
B-Besides, why would I care?
I dunno, why would you?
Aw! Don't answer a question
with another question!
Come on, we better hurry before
the lunch crowds fill everywhere up!
But why would you?!
Manager!
The manager found out you're an otaku?
I got careless.
How'd that even happen?
Did he see something you were drawing...?
Not exactly.
Shinozaki knows I'm an otaku,
but not about the cosplay stuff.
I don't really think him knowing
is a problem, though.
Well... maybe not a big problem...
Not a serious one, but...
Cute... Cute... Cute...
If it's not a problem, then what's the issue?
You're right.
I guess I should be glad
he didn't see me drawing BL dojinshi.
Whacha talking about?
M-Manager?!
Did he hear all that?!
Are you here for lunch with Senpai?
Are you curious?
Not exactly... and why are you
grinning like that?
Do you mind if
we join you for lunch?
Oh, sure.
In that case, I wanna sit
next to Hayakawa-san!
Don't let it bug you.
What is up with you today?!
I wonder what I should get.
I'm curious, Hayakawa-san.
What's BL?
W-Well, it's, er... it is sort of a...
What's wrong, Hayakawa-san?
You've gone bright red.
I-I-I wonder why.
Is it okay if I make this picture
my home screen background?
Of course not!
My Tiny Senpai.
Shinozaki-san!
Trick or treat!
Happy Halloween, Shinozaki-san!
Senpai!
It's Halloween, after all.
What do you think?
It's cu—er, very nice looking.
I was kinda surprised.
That being the case,
once again: trick or treat!
S-Sorry, I didn't get anything ready...
That's okay.
Here you go!
Oh, thank yo—
T-Trick or treat?
Well done! Here you go.
Come on, don't treat me like a kid.
What are you grinning about?
And with cat ears on.
Which one would you like?
Just thinking how this is going to be
one sugary Halloween!
By the way, Hayakawa-san.
Happy Halloween!
Yep, I was right. Your cat-like
nature makes it a good fit.
And we match!
M-Manager! Wearing cat ears at work is...
*Can't bring herself to take them off
The trick to happiness is a bowl of candy!
I love Halloween!
It's pretty great.
It's not a good idea to
overindulge on sweets, though.
Right! It can cause all kinds of problems.
But it's Halloween, so what can you do?
True.
That also applies to Christmas, Valentine's,
birthdays, and Hinamatsuri.
Agreed!
That's a lot of exceptions!
Senpai, did you try these chocolates?
Not yet.
They're pretty good.
They've got a more mature taste.
A mature taste?
I-Is she...?
Sh-She's waiting for me to
feed her the chocolate?
But if I do that...
M-My finger might touch Senpai's mouth!
But a chance like this...
Yoink.
Too bad. Time's up.
Yummy!
I'm so stupid! I wasted my chance!
Shinozaki-san...
I-I feel weirdly toasty now.
Shinozaki, is there any candy left?
Hayakawa-shan! Hayakawa-shan!
Smooch! Smooch! Smooch!
What's going on with Katase-san?
Don't go!
She just had one of these chocolates...
Chocolate?
Oh, these have alcohol in them.
Who could get that drunk off
of one chocolate?
Smooooch!
Would someone please help me?!
Who would've guessed that
Katase-san would turn
into a kissing machine
when she gets drunk?
A kissing machine...
Does that mean I've got a chance?!
Shinozaki-san...
Uh, well, I—I wasn't thinking
anything naughty!
Stare...
Could you at least say something?
Sorry, sorry!
Is that...
Manager! Manager!
Manager...
To be honest, I...
There's something I need to tell you.
Senpai! Senpai! Our manager
doesn't photosynthesize.
Over there, see?
I'm right over here!
What's up?
Manager! Manager!
Manager... the truth is, there's
something I need to tell you...
Wait, is this going where I think it is?!
Are Senpai... and Manager going to...
K-K-K-Kiss?!
Manager...
No! Hold on, Senpai!
I am so, so grateful for the way that you
always, always work so hard for us,
and to get our work done!
She's bowing out of gratitude?!
Maybe it's less about kissing
and more about her emotions
towards people getting amplified?
Oh bless you, bless you, God and Manager!
Th-That might be it.
I'm partly glad, and partly disappointed...
Now, then, Katase-senpai,
your kohai's right over there.
My kohai?
Kohai, Kohai!
Hang on! Finding out
how she feels about me...
I-I'm not emotionally prepared for this!
U-Uh, Senpai, I...
Wha...?!
Tears?!
I-I'm so sorry! I know I'm always
causing trouble for you, Senpai!
It's not that.
You used to have no idea
what to do on your own,
but you're so capable now...
It makes me really happy, as your senpai!
So she's my mom?
But...
if you do need help,
you can always turn to me, okay?
S-Senpai...
I-I think I'm gonna get you some water!
You sit here and wait a sec!
Tasty.
'Kay!
Nice.
So Senpai thinks...
You used to have no idea
what to do on your own...
I'm a little disappointed,
but I'm still glad.
Katase-san, Katase-san.
What do you think about Shinozaki-kun
personally, and not as a coworker?
Senpai, I've got your water.
Shinozaki-san is...
When it comes to him... I'm not sure yet...
I thought I had her that time.
Never mind that! Could you
please delete that picture?
Which one do you mean?
The one with Katase-san and I... y'know...
This one?
Hurry up and delete it!
Can I use it on my home screen?
Of course not!
Bleary-eyed and not fully awake from a dream
I still can't bring myself
to drink that bitter coffee
So I sneakily toss in
two pinches of a sweet secret
And let it slowly spread throughout
There's a local bakery
that's only open sometimes
Where I once had some toast that glittered
What is it that makes it so satisfying?
Almost like magic
I find myself thinking about that kind of thing
How the small things can be the most precious
Deep inside my heart
It's ever so bittersweet
"Just being around you is enough"
Becomes my mantra
Baby like sugar
Baby you're the sugar